<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Data Science on Ha Dinh Insights</title>
    <link>/categories/data-science/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Data Science on Ha Dinh Insights</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/data-science/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>To ask the right question, that is an art</title>
      <link>/data-science/ask-the-right-question/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/data-science/ask-the-right-question/</guid>
      <description>If you don’t have time to read a full article, go to Solution.
A little story I just moved to Vancouver recently, for my Master of Data Science at University of British Columbia. On my way home from a brunch meeting, I met a stranger lady on the bus. She started the conversation:
  Lady: “Hey, do you know if I can take Sky Train from Broadway City Hall to Broadway-Commercial station?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Define Data Analysis Objectives and Write a Logical Report</title>
      <link>/data-science/objectives-and-logical-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/data-science/objectives-and-logical-report/</guid>
      <description>For many data analysis beginners, there seems to be so many stories we can tell from a data set, but too little time we have to analyze data and tell those stories in a reader-friendly way. Undoubtedly, many of us find ourselves lost in a middle of data maze, confusing what is the most effective strategy to tackle with this complexity. The secret sauce to solve this is no secret, since it has been stated in many articles or textbooks: Defining project objectives before you proceed with your analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>