<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ha Dinh Insights</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ha Dinh Insights</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Why consumers do what they do?</title>
      <link>/consumer-behavior/why-consumers-do-what-they-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/consumer-behavior/why-consumers-do-what-they-do/</guid>
      <description>Why over 60% of consumers use the same brands of products that their parents did? One of human predictable biases is ‘Status quo’ – resistance to change. Therefore, growing up with parents, consumers have created a strong behavior with brands that their parents used. And strong behavior is difficult to break.  These brands have some attributes that other brands do not have. Based on ‘status quo’ and available heuristics (when consumers use their memory of actual instances to make judgment), it is difficult for consumers to get enough positive thoughts for unfamiliar brands that drive them to change their behavior easily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From Commercials to Consumer Behaviour of FMCG</title>
      <link>/consumer-behavior/commercials-to-cb-of-fmcg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/consumer-behavior/commercials-to-cb-of-fmcg/</guid>
      <description>Among eleven top-rated Super Bowl commercials from 1989 to 2015, there are two commercials that give me the most impression. The first one is “2004: Bud Light - Owners demonstrate how their dogs fetch Bud Light”. The second one is “1994: Pepsi - A chimp experiment goes awry”. These two commercials have both similar and different techniques to nudge viewers, becoming so popular among them.
 Commercial Summary The Bud Light commercial is about two guys and his two dogs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To ask the right question, that is an art</title>
      <link>/data-science/ask-the-right-question/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/data-science/ask-the-right-question/</guid>
      <description>If you don’t have time to read a full article, go to Solution.
A little story I just moved to Vancouver recently, for my Master of Data Science at University of British Columbia. On my way home from a brunch meeting, I met a stranger lady on the bus. She started the conversation:
  Lady: “Hey, do you know if I can take Sky Train from Broadway City Hall to Broadway-Commercial station?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From Starbucks to Louis Vuitton, how consumer understanding transforms businesses</title>
      <link>/consumer-behavior/how-consumer-understanding-transforms-businesses/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/consumer-behavior/how-consumer-understanding-transforms-businesses/</guid>
      <description>I travelled to Sydney, Australia during December 2016 for 10 days. It was for a study abroad trip with University of Cincinnati, Department of Economics to learn about economics of immigration. Besides knowledge of immigration problems and how Australia’s government is dealing with them, I gained great consumer insights through conversations and observation. 
Sydney is such a vibrant and metropolitan city with (especially) so many Asian. As a big fan of culinary, I discovered some café and restaurants around the city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Define Data Analysis Objectives and Write a Logical Report</title>
      <link>/data-science/objectives-and-logical-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/data-science/objectives-and-logical-report/</guid>
      <description>For many data analysis beginners, there seems to be so many stories we can tell from a data set, but too little time we have to analyze data and tell those stories in a reader-friendly way. Undoubtedly, many of us find ourselves lost in a middle of data maze, confusing what is the most effective strategy to tackle with this complexity. The secret sauce to solve this is no secret, since it has been stated in many articles or textbooks: Defining project objectives before you proceed with your analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>